We will see the importance of the influence of this plication,
この折りたたみの影響の重要性を見ていきましょう。
so of this flexion of the embryo,
つまり、胚のこの屈曲が、
at the level of the upper part of the intestine.
腸の上部でどのように作用するかです。
The embryo makes a flexion movement.
胚は屈曲運動をします。
Now, if I take this image,
さて、この画像を見て、
and I go back.
巻き戻しをします。
I do it like this here.
このようにします。
I go back, I do this.
巻き戻しをして、こうします。
By the covering of the embryo,
胚の被覆によって、
the mesenchyme, so the mesenchymal tissue,
間葉、つまり間葉組織が、
sub-mesencephalic,
中脳下部で、
perpendicular to the longitudinal axis, we see that it makes this
縦軸に対して垂直に、この動きをしているのがわかります。
movement there, hop, it gives this beautiful curvature, this orientation will
この動きが、この美しい湾曲を与え、この向きが、
give a
ここに、
compression here between the front and the back, gives the
前と後ろの間に圧縮を与え、それが、
base of the skull which is
頭蓋底を形成します。
a dynamic movement, there is a field here, it creates a cartilaginous field at the
これは動的な動きであり、ここに場があり、それが軟骨の場を形成します。
beginning, it's a bit like an axe, and then through this movement it
最初は少し斧のような形をしていて、この動きによって、
gives itself
それが形成され、
and makes primitive, compressed cartilages.
圧縮された原始軟骨が作られます。
Its expression will be a strong release of energy.
その表現は、強いエネルギーの放出となるでしょう。
Here, I have the amniotic cavity, vitelline cavity.
ここに羊膜腔と卵黄腔があります。
Now, I take here just the yellow,
さて、ここでは黄色い部分だけを取り上げ、
and I take here the yolk sac with the endoderm that is above.
その上にある内胚葉を含む卵黄嚢を取り上げます。
Now, we are in this developmental movement of the embryo
さて、私たちは胚の発生のこの動きの中にいます。
where it makes this flexion movement.
胚がこの屈曲運動をする中で。
So, I have my vitelline cavity.
つまり、私の卵黄腔があります。
here, ok, vitelline cavity it's there, then it will be found
ここに、はい、卵黄腔はここにあり、その後、
there, my neural tube which
そこに行き着きます。私の神経管は、
comes to coil up, at the beginning I have the cardiac zone which is quite anterior. The flexion movement
巻き付いてきます。最初は心臓領域がかなり前方にあります。胚の
of the embryo, we will study it from the periphery towards
屈曲運動は、周辺から
the inside,
内部へと研究されます。
so from the visible face, we can touch in the mouth up
つまり、目に見える面から、口の中を触れるところから、
to the level of the pharyngeal
腸のレベルまで、
intestine. This flexion movement,
咽頭までです。この屈曲運動は、
organizes this particularity of my face, from the periphery, towards
私の顔のこの特殊性を、周辺から
the inside.
内部へと組織化します。
It is my notochord that induces my neural tube, which induces my
私の脊索が私の神経管を誘導し、それが私の
arteries,
動脈を誘導し、
and it is the coiling around my arterial system that comes to organize itself.
そして私の動脈系を囲む巻き付きが組織化されていきます。
So, at first, schematically, I observe that the upper part
それで、まず、模式的に、私は上部が
of my intestine
私の腸の
is an articulation that is made.
関節になっていることを確認します。
between my heart and my brain.
私の心臓と脳の間で。
I now have this little
今、この小さなものが
thing that appears, the foregut, here,
現れています、前腸、ここに、
that appears, the upper intestine
現れている、上部腸が
that forms,
形成されています、
here. It's an articulation
ここに。これは関節です
between the heart
心臓と
and the brain
脳の間の
that develops here, you see, there.
ここで発達しているのがわかりますね。
Oriented, organized in space-time
羊水によって
by the amniotic fluid,
時空間に方向付けられ、組織化されていますが、
but whose fulcrum
その支点となるのは
is the vascular
血管系です。
system. This is my...
これは私の卵黄嚢です。ここには心臓があり、
yolk sac. There's the heart that's here,
ここには心臓があり、
which we see very high there, which we see here,
非常に高く見えますね、ここに見えます、
and we see
そして、
the coiling here, you see,
ここに巻きつきが見えますね、
and we see that it is an articulation
そして、それが心臓と
between the heart
心臓と
and the developing
発達中の脳の間の
brain.
関節であることがわかります。
It is he who will delimit the space
それが、私の卵黄嚢の
of the part
前部の
of my yolk sac in its anterior part
空間を区切って、
to form
この小さなループを形成します。
The more it continues, the more it will organize itself.
それが進むにつれて、さらに組織化されていきます。
Here I have the large yolk sac, and then finally I have the vestige of this yolk sac which is here.
ここに大きな卵黄嚢があり、最終的にその卵黄嚢の痕跡がここにあります。
And so I see that this upper part here will organize itself in these flexion movements.
そして、この上部が屈曲運動の中で組織化されていくのがわかります。
Amniotic cavity, we see the heart, and you see, look here, the space that will be created.
羊膜腔、心臓が見えますね、そしてここを見てください、形成される空間を。
It is an articulation between the heart and the brain, driven by amniotic
これは心臓と脳の間の関節であり、羊水の成長によって推進されます。
growth.
羊水の成長によって推進されます。
And here I have the beginning of the formation.
そして、ここに形成の始まりがあります。
Formation of my digestive tract which organizes itself on a longitudinal plane.
縦方向に組織化される消化管の形成。
It is the delimitation here that is made.
ここで境界が作られます。
It is the entire organization of my digestive tract that begins to take shape.
私の消化管全体の組織化が始まりつつあります。
Formation of the upper part of my intestine.
私の腸の上部の形成。
Integration of the allantois, the cloacal membrane that will form here.
ここに形成される卵黄嚢、総排出腔膜の統合。
And between this membrane here, here will be made.
そして、この膜とこの膜の間で、ここに形成されます。
develop the pharyngeal membrane, so the anlage at the
咽頭膜が発達し、口腔レベルでの原基となります。
oral level. We see clearly,
口腔レベル。よく見てください。
look closely, how it is an articulation between the brain, the
よく見てください、脳と羊膜嚢、心臓の間の関節がどのように形成されているか。
amniotic sac, the heart
羊膜嚢、心臓
as a fulcrum, organized by the differential growth rate
支点として、私の血管系の異なる成長速度によって組織化されています。
of my vascular
私の血管系の
system. It is a balance between my brain and my heart.
血管系。それは私の脳と私の心臓の間のバランスです。
oriented by my mesoderm, by the fluidic side of my mesoderm,
私の中胚葉によって、私の中胚葉の流動的な側面によって方向付けられています。
or in other words, by the vascular side of my mesoderm.
言い換えれば、私の中胚葉の血管の側面によって。
The appearance of a vessel is always dependent on different components.
血管の出現は常に異なる要素に依存しています。
A field, a metabolic concentration, a trajectory, vacuolizations
場、代謝濃度、軌道、空胞化
and the presence of interstitial particles.
そして間質粒子の存在。
It is a component that appears and disappears.
それは現れては消える要素です。
That's why in your embryo, you can have vessels that arrive
だから、あなたの胚には血管が現れることがあります。
over time you have vessels that disappear. That's why it comes from the periphery towards
時間が経つと血管が消えます。だから、それは周辺から中心に向かってきます。
the center. Pages and two vessels, two large aortas, and then which come to center
中心へ。2つの血管、2つの大きな大動脈、そしてそれが中心に集まってきます。
into one aorta. The influence of this plication will organize the internal delimitation
1つの大動脈に。この折り畳みの影響は、上部消化管の内側の境界を組織化します。
of the upper
管の
digestive tract. We will now go into the details.
上部消化管。それでは、詳細に入りましょう。